"Fluffy bangs soften your face and
allow you to softly capture her heart."
Mold
pure pureparato
Pre! Preparation!
tsuyoku nanka naikedo
I might not be very strong,
pure pureparedo
Pre! Pre-parade!
itsuka kimiwo tsukamaeru
but I'm gonna catch you
one of these days.
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
warete baribari
Cracking and crumbling.
pu re purepa pu re purepa pu re purepa
yudan shitara sono yubi
chiku chiku atakku kakugo shite
Let your guard down and expect
a poking attack from my fingers.
chiisai kedo hasamuno
mijinko mitai na anata
I may be small, but I can still
pluck you like a flea.
hoshiinowa purasuchikkuna haato
(purasu purasu dakedo mainasu)
I'm longing for a plastic heart.
(Plus, plus, somehow a minus)
demo soreja tsumaranai
sokoni kizuita monogachi
But the one who realizes how
boring that'd be will win.
koiwa amakute nigaimono
Love is so bittersweet.
tanjun meikai hukuzatsu kaikina shiromono
Plain and simple while
complicated and mysterious.
doudemoii kotobakkari
kinishitari suruno
You get worried about
the most pointless things.
donna kanji sonna kanji
How does it feel? THAT's how it feels.
onkou tokujitsu
ekisentorikku na anata
You are gentle and
sincere yet eccentric.
tsuyogaru soburiwo
zenshin matotte tachiuchi
I act tough as we butt heads.
I get dizzy whenever I try
to be honest to myself.
sunaona dakedato shigekigai
tsuyokute kurakura
I get hurt. You get hurt.
Innocent preparation.
kizutsui chauno kizutsuke chauno
junjou pureparato
In my mind, I'm always alone
on an innocent Pre-Parade.
atamano nakawa itsumo hitorino
junjou pureparedo
Tiger and Dragon
Takasu Residence
That thing
Heat before you eat
-Ryu
Ohashi High School
General Affairs - Lost and Found
Fierce as a tiger
But small
Cruisin' Tunes - Spring
From: Aisaka Taiga
(If you don't want this, throw it away.)
Takasu Yasuko - Stage name: Mirano
"On the Clock"
For: Kushieda Minori
From: Takasu Ryuji
To: Mr. Kitamura Yusaku
banira sorutode
Add vanilla salt.
BURNING LOVE
Burning love.
amai dakenara
If it's too sweet,
soruto kakemashou
we can add some salt.
dareyorimo motto motto watashiwo
I tell you all these things because
shitte hoshii kara sarake dashitai
I want you to know me
better than anyone else.
demo dekinaino keiken NOTHING
But nothing works when
I have no experience.
modokashi sugiru
This is so frustrating.
demo amaidakeno aiwa chotto
But a love that's purely sweet
watashiga motometeiru
monotowa chigau
isn't quite the love I'm looking for.
shiroto iwaretara
If you say white,
kurodatte icchau
I say black.
sunaoni narenai
A little imp
amanojaku
who can't be honest to herself.
sukito iwaretara
If you say love,
daikirai datte
I say hate.
ureshii noni nani ittendarou
Why do I say that when
I'm actually happy?
amai banirani
It's like adding salt
soruto kakeru youni
to sweet vanilla...